Fernando Ascencio

UNITY, AR AND MOBILE DEVELOPER

Portfolio



fhazel.com.mx

Contact



+52 3334953311



fernandohazel1@gmail.com



Guadalajara, Mexico, Zapopan Jal.



<u>fernandohab</u>



<u>FernandoHazel</u>

Languages

Spanish: English: Native Advanced

Skills

Unity Git

NET MAUI Scrum

C# Firebase

Kotlin Swift

SOL

Node Js

-....

Express js

HTML / CSS/ JS

React

Education

Bachelor in Digital Animation Tecnológico de Monterrey | January 2018 - December 2022

Videogame Developer Diploma Tec De Monterrey | February 2021 - May 2021

Full Stack Developer Diploma Digital House | April 2021 - August 2021

Unity Programmer Diploma
Unity Technologies | November 2022

About me

I am a 3 years experience developer which have worked in videogames, AR and mobile apps. My stack is Unity, Net MAUI, Kotlin, Swift and SQL but I started my coding journey with Nodejs and React before discovering my passion for mobile apps.

Professional Experience

Mobile Game Developer

One Simple Game Guadalajara. JAL | February 2022 - August 2022

- Collaborated with designers to implement new mechanics using C# applying OOP and design patterns
- Created a fully responsive UI an UX experience with Unity canvas
- Documented code for better workflow
- Tested and fixed bugs resulting in a 90% reduction of bugs
- Added analytics sdk to track the user actions in the game
- Had daily scrum sessions to ensure a better team communication
- · Used Git to ensure version control and safer workflow

AR and Mobile Developer

GSN Qro. Qro | November 2022 - May 2023

- Collaborated with product team to implement specifications using C#
- Consumed REST APIs with JSON and perfing CRUD to display, modify and store data
- Created a responsive UI and UX experience for IOS and Android
- · Used Git to ensure a better and safer workflow
- Tested and fixed bugs to ensure hight quality
- Created internal company apps for Grupo Bimbo, Ferromex and Silberhorn with unity for staff training and managment.
- Created an internal app with .NET MAUI for employees which improved the internal company efficiency and comunication

Bussiness Owner

Fhazel Solutions Tech | From December 2021

- Created responsive web sites for bussiness using HTML and CSS deployed with vercel
- Created multiplatform mobile app for a restaurant using .NET MAUI which improved user experience when buying food and drinks
- Creating and monetizing my own mobile games for Android and IOS using unity, one is already on production
- Creating and monetizing my own apps using Kolin and swift
- Applying Ad Mob, IAP and Firebase Analytics to monetize, track results and find bugs
- Updating youtube videos teaching others programming fundamentals and technologies curiosities
- I give private programming classes of Unity, Git, Nodejs and React
- Working on a football club app with Kotlin and Swift
- Working on a transportation app with Kotlin and Swift
- Working on a football training app with Kotlin and Swift
- Leaded a team using scrum which published 2 videogames